The cure to the pain was to know how to put it into language, 
once you could translate the suffering into insight it burned less.


Because I was the world's greatest psychiatrist 
and had long ago initiated an experiment operating in the real world.

I would give subconscious cues to people to behave in certain ways 
and treat me in certain ways:
this treatment would dictate my behavior 
and I'd prove once and for all that behavior is
circumstantially induced. Further, by encouraging 
people to abuse me I was gaining experiential
knowledge of the world: a first hand account 
of how things felt on the interior and my unique
power of introspection 
would translate those experiences 
into general knowledge for the masses,
once the experiment was done.